Previously on JoJo's Bizarre Adventure!
Come out.
It's time to go home.
Ugh, get lost.
I didn't ask you to come here.
You really think you can help me?
I'd like you to meet an Egyptian
friend I met a few years ago.
Say hello to Avdol.
Red Boy!
Huh? What the?
And now for the truth.
This may seem like an evil
spirit, but it's far from it.
Jotaro,
this thing you believe has possessed
you is actually a powerful vision,
created by your own life energy.
This vision will always
appear standing by your side.
And because of that, we call it a stand!
That coffin's a hundred years
old, and four years ago,
it was pulled out of the
Atlantic, off the coast of Africa.
Okay, so?
I did a little research.
My grandfather, Jonathan Joestar, your
great-grandfather, died while at sea.
Turns out this exact same coffin was
on that boat with him when he died.
When they discovered it four
years ago, it was empty,
but I know exactly what was inside it.
Avdol and I are trying to
locate him as we speak.
That person is evil incarnate!
And his name is Theo!
And now that he has been awakened
from his hundred-year slumber,
it is our fate to fight that man!
From the neck of this bastard
on down is Jonathan Joestar!
My grandfather!
This son of a bitch took over his body!
Jotaro, don't leave yet.
You forgot something important.
Silly boy.
Here is your goodbye kiss.
You're such a bitch.
Stop clinging to me like
I'm still a little kid.
Okay.
Have a nice day.
What a giant pain in my ass.
Hey, look, it's Jojo! What? Jojo?
You're right, it is Jojo!
Jojo! Jojo! Hey, Jojo!
What's up, Jojo?
Hey there, Jojo!
What's going on, Jojo?
So tell me, Jojo, where have you been?
You haven't been to school for four days!
Hey!
Who do you think you are,
grabbing off to Jojo like that?
I don't like how friendly
you're getting with him.
Stay away!
What the hell, ugly?
I'd be careful there.
No boobs.
Ugly... No boobs... Ugly... Ugly...
Ugly...
supplemental...
Shut up!
You're freaking annoying!
aggh, he totally said that to me!
Uh, me...
JoJo...
What the hell?
Those branches.
Jojo!
Oh, no!
Jojo fell so far, you're almost up!
Look, he can still move.
The branches must have broken his fall.
Did a branch slash open my leg?
No, wait a sec.
That's not what caused me
to fall down the stairs.
This cut is what came first. But how?
I see.
Looks like he's able to
summon a pretty fierce stand.
I get it now.
Impressive.
No wonder he wants me to get rid of him.
But still...
He is no match for the power of my stand.
You really scared me are you okay
Jojo you think you're hurt anywhere
you're lucky if you had landed just a
few inches off you'd have cracked your
head right on the flagstone nasty
accidents happen on those steps all the
time tomorrow when you go down these
steps you really should hold my hand
Here.
Your leg seems to be cut.
You might want to wrap it with this
handkerchief to help stop the bleeding.
You going to be okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
It's just a scratch.
Hold it.
I forgot to say thanks.
Haven't seen you before.
You go to our school?
I'm Noriyaki Kakyoin.
And yes, I just
transferred here yesterday.
See you around.
Oh. Oh. Oh.
So his name's Kakyoin. Seems
pretty cool. You think so?
I still like Jojo way more than him.
Yeah, me too.
Same goes for me.
At that time I was very weak
lacking a body made me vulnerable
If I had not taken Jonathan Joestar's body
If it hadn't been for
his energy to augment
my own limited source I
couldn't have survived
at the bottom of that
ocean for a hundred years.
But still, this body has
like a bond between a
parent and a child.
It ties me to his kin.
They seem to know of my existence.
And of this power I've gained
from taking Jonathan's body,
the stand.
It is the stand that reaches out
to the bodies of his descendants.
There are always advantages and
disadvantages to every situation.
I will eliminate them all.
The Joestar clan must be destroyed soon.
Why is every single room in
this house so tiny and cramped?
This is exactly why I hate Japan.
Avdol, how the hell can
you stand being here?
I find it quite fascinating.
Especially the tea ceremony.
Ceremony shmarimony.
Instant coffee will do just fine.
By the way, about Dio.
Mr.
Joestar, If you and I are
aware of his existence,
would it not be safe to assume
that he knows about us as well?
Hmm.
But if we don't know
what he's going to do,
or for that matter, even
what powers he has...
Japanese coffee is absolutely vile!
That's American coffee.
That's a horrible cut, Jojo.
How'd you get it?
Let me guess, you got into
another fight, didn't you?
Show some respect and take off that hat.
It's poor manners.
Would you stop that? Seriously?
Has Jojo ever been hurt in a fight before?
That's not what cut him, I'm sure. No way.
Well, you do have a point.
Then I'll assume you were
being clumsy, you big klutz.
Hey, hold on.
What are you gonna do?
Cut your pants, of course.
Like hell you are.
Well, if I'm going to
treat that wound, I must.
You ruin him.
I'll take him off.
Didn't know you were so thrifty.
So, while JoJo's taking off his pants,
I'm going to take your temperatures?
and prove you're nothing
but a bunch of fakers.
Come on, we really caught a cold.
Totally.
Now just let us go home already.
Not going to happen.
Oops.
What the hell is this?
Kaku-yoo-yoo.
Hey, doctor!
What are you trying to do?
What does it look like?
I'm just shaking out the
thermometer to reset it!
That's not a thermometer
you got in your hand!
Yeah, that's a pen! Oh, come on!
Did you just say pen?
You think I'm dumb?
Does this look like a pen to you?
Tell me something, just how
stupid are you two boys?
If you honestly think this thermometer
I'm holding looks like a pen to you,
then maybe you need to take a closer look!
What the...
My eyes!
It's in my eyes!
Jojo, what do you have to say?
You're not gonna stand there and tell me
this thermometer looks like a pen too,
are you?
What the hell is going on?
Such strength, this is no mere woman.
Wait, I saw something weird
crawling up on the floor.
Was it a stand?
Noriyaki Kakyoin.
Was he the one who started this?
Did he cut my leg on the stone steps?
Yes, it was me.
So it is you.
Hey, long time no see.
So my stand is currently possessing
and controlling that doctor.
If you attack my stand,
you'll hurt her too, Jojo.
You bastard.
Who are you?
I told you, I'm Noriyaki Kakyoin.
And the name of my stand
here is Hierophant Green.
I am human, but I have
pledged loyalty to him.
That's why I'm gonna kill you.
I have zero intention of hurting her.
Now that I've dragged it
out, I see it for what it is.
Just a sleazy stand whose only
ability is to possess people.
So this is your stand? Kakyoin?
This green stripy thing
looks like a shiny melon.
You're gonna regret doing that.
Dragging that out of
her was a mistake, Jojo.
Don't act tough.
I can see my finger
marks on your forehead.
If I decide to crush your Stan's
head like the melon it is,
then I'm guessing your
head will get crushed too.
I'm gonna keep a tight
grip on you for now.
We're gonna pay my Gramps a little visit.
I'm sure he'd love to meet you.
But I'd like to know
more about Dio myself.
What the hell was that
green liquid coming out
of his stand's hand you
should have listened!
Jojo I told you you're
gonna regret this didn't
I this is the attack of
my stand hierophant green!
No weird moves kakyoin.
Emerald Splash!
So what do you think?
Did you like Emerald Splash?
That fluid you saw in Hierophant Green is
actually a surge of destructive energy.
It tore straight through
your stand's chest.
And your insides have
now been torn to shreds.
And as for that doctor over there...
Why?
I know I took that stand
out of her. So how?
I told you already.
But let me reiterate.
I tried to warn you that by
attacking my hierophant green it
would hurt her as well My stand
can travel farther than yours,
but it dislikes open
spaces without exception.
It prefers to hide within something
If you drag it out, it gets angry.
That's why when you ripped it out of
her throat it hurt her along the way?
You're the one who did this to her.
This is entirely your fault.
Jojo.
You must be held responsible
Look at what you've done!
All you had to do was let me kill you and
the doctor would have
walked away unharmed.
And still, you get up.
You are so pathetic.
You're nothing more than a sandbag
about to be pummeled by a skilled boxer.
Why even bother standing up?
I'm just gonna knock you down again.
Look no one ever said
Jotaro Kujo was a nice guy
I beat the crap out of
people more than I have to.
Some are even still in the hospital
I've had idiot teachers who like
to talk big so I taught them a lesson
and they never came back to class.
If I go to a restaurant the food's bad.
and make it a policy to
stiff him with the bill.
But even a bastard like me
can spot true evil when he sees it.
True evil are those who
use the weak for their own
game and crush them underfoot
when they're through.
Especially an innocent woman.
And that is exactly what
you've done, isn't it?
And your stand gets to hide from the
victim, the law, and the consequences.
That's why I will judge you myself.
I'm evil. See?
That's where you're wrong.
Evil is always the loser.
It's the victor who has justice.
The victim being the last man standing.
And how you win in battle?
is irrelevant.
See, the loser is always the evil one.
Time to finish you off.
Really?
The loser's evil?
Emerald
Splash!
Then let me show you.
What?
There's no way!
No one can just deflect
the Emerald Splash!
Just how evil you are!
I'll teach you justice...
...with my stat!
Your stand has incredible power.
You caught me by surprise earlier
and scratched its chest a little.
I'm glad my stand isn't weak,
but sometimes it feels like it
can get more savage than I am.
That was a close call.
She'll be fine once
her wounds are treated.
Did a gaspike just burst?
He came from the doctor's office!
Everyone, stay in the classroom!
I'll leave the cleanup to them.
They've had enough school for one day.
This guy needs to talk.
I want to hear everything
he knows about Dio.
I just have the most amazing
connection with my son right now.
Jotaro must be thinking about
me at school this very second.
I'm not thinking about you.
Jotaro!
Why aren't you at school?
And who is that boy on your shoulder?
Is that blood that he's covered in?
Wait a sec.
Please don't tell me you did that.
None of your business.
I need to find the old man.
Finding someone in this
big house really sucks.
I think you can find him
with Abdul right now.
They're both in the tea room.
Oh, Jotaro.
You never tell me anything.
All that does is make me
worry about you all the time.
But still, I know that deep
down you really do mean well.
You're a very sweet little boy at heart.
Hey? Yes?
You're looking a little bit
pale this morning You alright?
Yay!
I'm fine! Thank you!
I knew it.
Well, I hate to say it, but
But it's too late for him.
There's no way he'll make it.
He's got a few days
before he dies at most.
Jotaro, this is not your fault. Trust me,
do you want to know why this man swore his
allegiance to Dio and came
to your school to kill you?
Look right here, and I will show you!
What the hell is that?
This is very bad.
At this rate.
A little cold isn't bad from time to time.
I have no idea why I want to either.
This is the one thing I feared the most.
Tell me, what can we do?